resource.org 2011-12-09

# The Public.Resource.Org Privacy Policy

This policy discloses what information we gather about you when you visit any of our Web sites (all Public.Resource.Org, Pacer.Resource.Org, Bulk.Resource.Org, and other network sites). It describes how we use that information and how you can control it. Our privacy policy addresses:

Information Public.Resource.Org gathers and tracks  
Personal information  
Aggregated tracking information  
Cookies  
Third Party Cookies  
Third Party Advertising  
Notification of Changes  
How to update, correct, or delete your information

## Information Public.Resource.Org gathers and tracks

Public.Resource.Org collects two kinds of information about users: 1) data that users volunteer by signing up to receive news, participate in discussion groups, completing surveys, or donate to us; and 2) aggregated tracking data we collect when users interact with us. 

## Personal information

We use the personal information you provide voluntarily to send information you've requested. The specific use of your personal information varies, depending on how you contact us:

  * When you sign up online to receive Public.Resource.Org Network newsletters, Public.Resource.Org product and company news, and to participate in talkbacks on our sites you must provide your name, email address, and a password. We never sell or rent your email address or other personally identifiable information you provide us under these circumstances.
  * When you register for an Public.Resource.Org conference, or sign up for a conference email list, we will send you email announcements and updates about Public.Resource.Org conferences. We send conference brochures to past conference attendees.

We share your information only as described below: 

  * We release personal information when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Public.Resource.Org Media, our users, or others. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Aggregated tracking information

We analyze visitors' use of our sites by tracking information such as pageviews, traffic flow, search terms, and click through. We use this information to improve our sites. We also share this anonymous traffic and demographic information in aggregate form with partners and funders. We do not share any information that can identify an individual user.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser when you visit our sites. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your computer, so that we can provide you with personalized information and features. We also use cookies to track user traffic patterns.

You can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies or to block cookies. If you block cookies, you may not be able to use certain site features or functions. 

## Third Party Cookies

We do not use third party cookies.

## Third Party Advertising

We do not use third party advertising.

## Notification of Changes

This privacy policy was put in effect on January 1, 2008.

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on public.resource.org. If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via email. Users will be able to opt out of any new use of their personal information.

## How to update, correct, or delete your information

**Email** : To get help from a human, send email to carl [at] media [dot] org.

**Snailmail** : To reach us with written communications via postal mail, please send mail to Public.Resource.Org, 1005 Gravenstein Highway North, Sebastopol, CA. 95472.
